# Amanda Molde

# Full-Stack Web Developer

Denver, CO 80129 | 303-589-2498 | amanda.molde@gmail.com amandamolde.com | linkedin.com/in/amandamolde | github.com/amandamolde

### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Web Developer with an engineer's mindset. Sees structure where none is apparent, adept at solving problems under constraints, and able to make considered judgments between alternative ideas. Experience in testing and design of a real-estate finance product in an agile scrum environment.

### **SKILLS**

JavaScript | ¡Query | Node.js | Express | React | MongoDB Python | Django | PostgreSQL | HTML | CSS | Bootstrap

# **APPS & WEBSITES**

## Writer's Bloa

- Full CRUD application that allows users to create, edit, and delete blog posts and comments
- API endpoints with two routes for each model one for the list view and one for the single view
- Responsible for API back-end and troubleshooting edit modals on the front-end
- Skills: Python | Django | React | PostgreSQL | Reactstrap | HTML | CSS

#### e-Commerce Clone

- Back-end API that serves JSON to the front-end
- Front-end React application that updates the UI and makes requests to the API
- User authentication using Auth0 and an admin inventory management panel
- Skills: Node.js | Express | React | MongoDB | Reactstrap | HTML | CSS

### pastTents

- Campsite review application with 3<sup>rd</sup> party authentication using Passport.js
- Integrated database models with reviews that display for each campsite
- Skills: Node is | Express | Mongoose | MongoDB | Bootstrap | HTML | CSS

### **Farkle**

- Browser-based clone of the classic dice game
- · 2-player with complex scoring logic
- Skills: JavaScript I jQuery I Bootstrap I HTML I CSS

### Tamagotchi

- Browser-based remake of the handheld digital pet
- Virtual pet gets hungry, sleepy, and bored at timed intervals
- Skills: JavaScript | Bootstrap | HTML | CSS

# Amanda Molde

# Full-Stack Web Developer

Denver, CO 80129 I 303-589-2498 I amanda.molde@gmail.com amandamolde.com I linkedin.com/in/amandamolde I github.com/amandamolde

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Business Analyst / Jr. Product Owner

Sep 2017 - Apr 2018

ProLink Solutions, Englewood, CO

- Researched client requirements and transformed them into viable software design for 3 products
- Spearheaded data migration mapping, resulting in a 30% decrease in implementation hours
- · Created design prototypes for stakeholders with Axure RP
- Used Microsoft Team Foundation Server (TFS) for backlog management and work item tracking

# **Quality Assurance Analyst**

Jun 2017 - Sep 2017

ProLink Solutions, Englewood, CO

- Identified and analyzed problems with software application function, output, display, and content
- Supplied designers and developers with recommendations on software usability and functionality
- Created test cases within Microsoft Team Foundation Server (TFS) linking to the user story
- Supported company initiative to document automated test cases

# Sales Support Specialist

Mar 2016 - Jun 2017

Level 3 Communications, Broomfield, CO

- Supported 3 general managers and 25+ account directors while negotiating with outside vendors
- Created a spreadsheet to compare pricing for multiple sites (1000+) with up to 40 vendor bids each

# **Process Engineer**

Feb 2012 - Mar 2016

AECOM, Greenwood Village, CO

- Designed, evaluated, and implemented solutions to complex problems using engineering principals
- Analyzed systems to determine how changes in conditions and operations would affect outcomes
- · Identified strengths and weaknesses of potential solutions or approaches using logic and reasoning
- Trained a team of 20 people how to use a new software system that was required by the client
- Coordinated an office event for 2 years with a 25% budget savings the 2<sup>nd</sup> year

## Market Analyst

Jul 2011 - Feb 2012

National Fuel Marketing, Centennial, CO

- Gathered and assessed data on production, markets, and transportation of crude oil products
- Managed the scheduling and distribution of propane inventories

### **EDUCATION**

General Assembly, Web Development Certificate, Denver, CO Colorado School of Mines, M.S., Engineering and Technology Management, Golden, CO Colorado School of Mines, B.S., Chemical Engineering, Golden, CO

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Certified Scrum Product Owner, CSPO, Scrum Alliance